<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_1">Picking fruit and logs off the ground will get you far in this place. Here is a milestone for gathering lots of stuff up.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_10">Planting seeds in the red dirt. They grow up so fast. Here is a milestone for planting some seeds.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_11">Watering plants is good for your soul and good for the plant's general health. It's win-win. So here is a milestone for watering a lot of plants!</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_12">Smashing rocks is hard work. But sometimes they have stuff in them! Here is a milestone for smashing rocks.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_13">You've smashed a couple of them rocks filled with ore. Here is a milestone for smashing ore deposits.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_14">Smelting. Oh, you've been smelting alright. Here is a milestone for smelting ore into bars.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_15">Grinding rocks down into powder. Here is a milestone for using a stone grinder a bunch.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_16">Sometime trees get in the way and sometimes you just need to borrow their wood for a bit. Here is a milestone for chopping down trees.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_17">You can't just chop a tree down and leave the stump. Here is a milestone for getting rid of the lil' stumps that are there after the tree falls down.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_18">You like wood, right? But what about square wood? Here is a milestone for cutting wood into planks.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_19">You've caught a bunch of fish. Here is a milestone for catching a bunch of fish!</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_2">Being friendly and making friends is an adventure on its own! Be sure to chat with everyone every day! You might learn something.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_20">No matter how much you clear it seems to come back. Mowing never ends. Here is a milestone for chopping grass.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_21">Hunting is sometimes necessary. Here is a milestone for hunting creatures.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_22">Trapping animals for relocation is a kind way to deal with them. It's not easy to do, either! Here is a milestone for trapping an animal.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_23">Buying furniture for your home? Maybe a gift? Here is a milestone for buying furniture.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_24">New walls. Same old house. Here is a milestone for buying wallpaper.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_25">Here is a milestone for buying flooring.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_26">Here is a milestone for buying seeds.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_27">Reap what you have sown. Here is a milestone for harvesting crops.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_28">Looking good in some new threads. Here is a milestone for buying clothes</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_29">Cooked fruit. Sounds gross, I know. It might be... Anyway, here is a milestone for cooking fruit.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_3">Catching bugs is a great activity. Here is a milestone for catching some of those creepy crawlies.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_30">Mixing things all together to make something? You're a bloody chef, I'll tell you what. Here is a milestone for cooking at the cooking table.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_31">Always replace what you've taken. Here is a milestone for planting tree seeds.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_32">What are fish doing in the ocean when they could be put to good use lining your pockets. Here is a milestone for selling fish.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_33">Bugs are everywhere. For some reason, John wants them. Here is a milestone for selling bugs.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_34">You've got to squeeze for every Dink you can. Even if it means dealing with shells. Here is a milestone for selling shells.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_35">Farming has paid off. You've reaped what you have sown. Here is a milestone for selling plants.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_36">There is stuff everywhere underground. Here is a milestone for digging up treasure.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_37">Bury fruit and get a fruit tree! You beauty! Here is a milestone for burying fruit.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_38">Here is a milestone for diving for treasure.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_39">You treat your feathered and furred friends well. Here is a milestone for petting your animals.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_4">Crafting useful things yourself is a handy skill in a place starting off with nothing. Here is a milestone for crafting items.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_40">You feed them every day so they will love you. Here is a milestone for feeding your animals.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_41">Deep down in the shifting mines, it's dangerous... but you've been there a bunch! Here is a milestone for entering the mines.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_42">You help anyone that asks, eh? Here is a milestone for doing a lot of favours.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_43">Being poisoned might not kill you, but it will take a lot of energy out of you. Here is a one time milestone for being poisoned. But try not to be from now on, okay?</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_44">You sure can take a hit or two. Here is a milestone for taking damage.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_45">Watch your health! Make sure to eat food that recovers health. Maybe have a sit down to recover faster? Here's a milestone for fainting, but try not to from now on. </string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_46">The more friendly you are with someone the more likely they will send you mail! Here is a milestone for receiving letters.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_47">From tent, to house to even bigger house! Here is a milestone for upgrading your home.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_48">Every adventure starts somewhere and yours starts here. Here is a milestone for placing the base tent.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_49">A place to rest your head - your new home for now. Here is a milestone for placing your tent.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_5">Fruit? Meat? Fungus? It doesn't matter. Food will give you energy to keep doing your tasks all day long. Here is a milestone for eating things!</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_50">Building the town - one building at a time. Here is a milestone for finishing a new building!</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_51">You can buy a lot of useful tools to help you! Here is a milestone for buying tools.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_52">What are these things even made of? Here is a milestone for breaking tools.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_53">You always go out of your way to help people who have posted on the bulletin board. Here is a milestone for completing tasks from the bulletin board.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_54">You make sure you document all the different bugs you've caught. Here is a milestone for adding new species of bugs to your Pedia.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_55">You make sure you document all the different fish you've caught. Here is a milestone for adding new species of fish to your Pedia.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_56">You are documenting all the wildlife here on the island. Here is a milestone for adding a new animal to your Pedia.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_57">Take those animal products and make them better! Here is a milestone for making something from animal products.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_58">They crack easy, but they sell for a bit! Here is a milestone for selling eggs.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_59">You've gotta give back after you take. Here is a milestone for planting wild seeds for grass, bushes and trees.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_6">Staying in one spot isn't generally considered exploring. You're going to cover some distance, that's for sure! Here is a milestone for travelling!</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_60">Pick up some dirt, put it there. Here is a milestone for moving soil.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_61">What if you take the tools from John's shop and make them better? Here is a milestone for upgrading tools.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_62">Travelling on foot is for fools. Here is a milestone for travelling in style via vehicle.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_63">Here is a milestone for getting haircuts.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_64">Saving money in the bank. Clever. Here is a milestone for having a cold hard Mil.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_65">Giving an animal a new home is a great thing. Here is a milestone for buying a new animal friend.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_66">Crab pots don't always catch crabs, but when they do, it's crab night! Here is a milestone for catching something in your crab pot.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_67">Milestone for selling fossils.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_68">Milestone for selling Wary Mu eggs.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_69">Beehives. You can smash 'em or sell them. Here is a milestone for selling a beehive.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_7">Nothing wrong with spending some of that hard-earned dosh. Here is a milestone for spending Dinks.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_70">Keeping your bee's happy and they will give you a little honey. Here is a milestone for collecting honey.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_71">Painting things gives them their own flair. Here is a milestone for making something your own with a nice paint job.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_72">Going on a fishing trip but you caught a shark. Crikey! Here is a milestone for reeling in a beast.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_73">Shells are nature's way of littering. Here is a milestone for picking up those bad boys.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_74">Why not make some tea in a Billy and then pop them in a keg? Here is a milestone for doing some brewing.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_75">Tele-Towers are handy. But are you still you? Oh well, here is a milestone for using the Tele-Towers.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_76">Plants love old stinky stuff. Poop. Bones. They love it all. Here is a milestone for using the composter.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_77">Move dirt from here to there. Here is a milestone for using a Wheelbarrow.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_78">Mowing the lawn. You're in suburbia now. Here is a milestone for mowing the law.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_79">A helicopter? It flies? Here is a milestone for flying like a bird.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_8">Making that bread. That cold hard cash. Nothing wrong with making a bit of a profit. Here is a milestone selling stuff for money.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_80">Now it's time to really farm. Here is a milestone for getting a tractor.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_81">A bucket on your head! You bloody galah. You're having a laugh. Here is a milestone for rockin a bucket on your head.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_82">Taking photos. Saving memories. Here is a milestone for taking some photos.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_83">Falling with style. Here is a milestone for hanging and gliding.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_84">Unlocking doors with your keys. Where does the key go? Who knows. Here is a milestone for using keys.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_85">Here is a milestone for milking Vombats.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_86">Here is a milestone for shearing Pleep.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_87">Here is a milestone for selling fruit.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_88">Here is a milestone for selling amber.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_89">Birthdays are special for some reason. Here is a milestone for giving a birthday gift to someone.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_9">Chuck another steak on the barbie, mate. A milestone for grilling up some meat to eat!</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_90">Here is a milestone for finding a gemstone and selling it.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_91">Sometimes the sky gets mad and starting throwing down bolts. Here is a milestone for getting hit by lightning.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_92">Here is a milestone for finding a Thunder Egg and selling it.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_93">Alpha animals cause havoc. Here is a milestone for defeating an Alpha animal.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_94">Why keep your fish in an aquarium when you could keep them in your belly? Here is a milestone for cooking fish.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_95">It's brave to dive down and grab a random critter with your bare hands. Here is a milestone for catching underwater critters.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_96">Bug Comps are serious business. No time for fun. Here is a milestone for placing in the Bug Comp.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_97">They aren't as pretty as vehicles, but riding an animal is good fun. Here is a milestone for riding an animal for a distance.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_98">Fishing Comps are come twice a year. Lots of time for fun. Here is a milestone for placing in the Fishing Comp.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_99">Sometimes, nature calls. And you have heard that call. Here is a milestone for using the dunny.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_100">Who isn’t above selling a rare space rock for some cash? Here is a milestone for selling a meteorite.</string>
  <string name="MilestoneDesc/MilestoneDesc_101">Be careful what you wish for… Or don't? Here is a milestone for making a wish at the Wish Fountain.</string>
</resources>